Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XCVI is arranged in 190 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XCVI. 1939 CONVENTION RESOLUTIONS
  - Sub-Series 475-0. 1939 Convention Resolutions. General
    - Supplement to Grand President's Bulletin, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 1)
      1939 June
    - General, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 475-1. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 1
    - Election of Express Vice-Grand President and Express Member Board of Trustees, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 475-2. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 2
    - Reduce Per Capita Tax to Grand Lodge on New and Reinstated Members, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 475-3. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 3
    - Express Agreement on Short-Hour Work, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 475-4. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 4
    - Hourly Employees, Pennsylvania Express Terminal, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 475-5. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 5
    - Express Agreement on Consolidation of Rosters, New York, New York Area, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 475-6. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 6
    - Express Agreement on Reduction of Period of Bulletined Positions., 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 475-7. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 7
    - Rule No. 21, Express Agreement, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 475-8. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 8
    - Starting Time, Express Agreement, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 475-9. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 9
    - Legal Holidays, Express Agreement, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 475-10. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 10
    - Rule No. 91, Express Agreement, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 475-11. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 11
    - Trainmen Handling Express Work, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 475-12. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 12
    - Failure to Bid of Furloughed Employees, Express Agreement, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 475-13. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 13
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Credit World War [I] Service, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 475-14. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 14
    - Vacations. Universal Carloading and Distributing Company, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 475-15. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 15
    - Crossing of Picket Lines by Brotherhood Members, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 475-16. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 16
    - Rule No. 21, Express Agreement, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 475-17. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 17
    - Pool Cars, Less-than-Carload Freight, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 475-18. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 18
    - Violating Rules Knowingly, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 475-19. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 19
    - Limiting Number of Excepted Positions., 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 475-20. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 20
    - Year Books, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 475-21. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 21
    - Wage Differential for Night Work, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 475-22. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 22
    - Pass Rights for Express Employees, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 475-23. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 23
    - Extra or Substitute Work, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 475-24. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 24
    - Alternate Delegates to Convention, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 475-25. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 25
    - Closed Shop and Forty-Hour Week, Express Employees, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 475-26. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 26
    - Holidays With Pay for Hourly Rated Employees, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 475-27. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 27
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Provide Full Annuity on Disability with 30 Years' Service, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 475-28. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 28
    - Elimination of Personal Office or Excepted Positions., 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 475-29. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 29
    - Retirement Legislation for Canadian Railway Employees, 1939-1940 (Box 608a, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 475-30. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 30
    - Organizing Campaign in Canada, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 475-31. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 31
    - Wage and Working Condition Agreements in Canada, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 475-32. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 32
    - Election of Officers on Third Day of Convention, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 475-33. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 33
    - Salaries of Officers Established Following Election, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 475-34. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 34
    - Increase in Salary for Grand Lodge Officers, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 475-35. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 35
    - Correspondence School Conducted By Grand Lodge, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 475-36. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 36
    - Colored Employees, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 475-37. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 37
    - Wages for Express Messengers, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 475-39. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 39
    - Pass Rights of Express Employees, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 475-41. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 41
    - Grand President's Weekly Radio Time, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 475-42. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 42
    - Express Cars Without Vestibule, 1939-1946 (Box 608a, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 475-43. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 43
    - Express Vice Grand President and Express Member, Board of Trustees, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 475-44. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 44
    - Agents at Non-Telegraphic Stations., 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 475-45. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 45
    - Short-Hour Work, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 475-46. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 46
    - Prohibition on Transferring Work to Other Crafts, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 475-47. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 47
    - Increase in Salaries of Grand Lodge Officers, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 475-48. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 48
    - National Uniform Agreements for All Transportation Companies, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 475-49. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 49
    - Brotherhood Northwestern Representative, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 475-50. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 50
    - Regulation of Assigned Hours, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 475-51. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 51
    - Annual Wage for Railroad Employees, 1939-1940 (Box 608a, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 475-52. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 52
    - Eliminate Employment of Married Women, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 475-53. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 53
    - Pass Rights of Express Employees, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 475-54. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 54
    - Pass Rights of Express Employees, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 475-55. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 55
    - Technological Unemployment, 1939-1948 (Box 608a, Folder 55)
    - Technological Unemployment. Papers and Exhibits Used by Grand President Harrison in Testimony Before Temporary National Economic Committee, 1940 (Box 608a, Folder 56)
      1940 April
  - Sub-Series 475-56. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 56
    - Technological Unemployment, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 475-57. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 57
    - Technological Unemployment, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 475-58. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 58
    - Technological Unemployment, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 475-59. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 59
    - Technological Unemployment, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 475-60. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 60
    - Technological Unemployment, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 475-61. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 61
    - Technological Unemployment, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 475-62. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 62
    - Technological Unemployment, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 475-63. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 63
    - Technological Unemployment, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 475-64. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 64
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Compel Retirement at Age 60, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 475-65. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 65
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Compel Retirement with 30 Years' Service and $100 Per Month Benefit, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 475-66. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 66
    - Increase in Salaries of Grand Lodge Officers, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 475-67. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 67
    - Vacation and Sick Leave, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 475-68. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 68
    - Uniform Vacation for All Employees, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 69)
  - Sub-Series 475-69. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 69
    - Prohibit Quitting Time Between Midnight and 5:00 am, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 70)
  - Sub-Series 475-70. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 70
    - New Deal Objectives Approved, 1939-1940 (Box 608a, Folder 71)
  - Sub-Series 475-71. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 71
    - Prohibit Quitting Time Between Midnight and 5:00 am, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 475-72. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 72
    - Increase in Salaries of Grand Lodge Officers, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 73)
  - Sub-Series 475-73. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 73
    - Mileage Base for Express Managers, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 74)
  - Sub-Series 475-74. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 74
    - Dee, R.P., 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 75)
  - Sub-Series 475-75. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 75
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford System Board of Adjustment, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 475-76. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 76
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Provide Annuities for the Retired and for the Disabled, Regardless of Age, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 77)
  - Sub-Series 475-77. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 77
    - Vacations, All Classes, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 78)
  - Sub-Series 475-78. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 78
    - Communism, Fascism, Nazism, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 79)
  - Sub-Series 475-79. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 79
    - Mileage Base for Express Messengers, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 80)
  - Sub-Series 475-80. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 80
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Provide Minimum Pension of $100 Per Month; Compulsory Retirement at Age 60 or Optional After 30 Years' Service; Pensions to Widows, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 81)
  - Sub-Series 475-81. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 81
    - Standard Sunday and Holiday Rule, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 82)
  - Sub-Series 475-82. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 82
    - Mileage Base For Express Messengers, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 83)
  - Sub-Series 475-83. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 83
    - Compensation of Express Messengers for Mail Handling, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 84)
  - Sub-Series 475-84. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 84
    - Express General Foremen, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 85)
  - Sub-Series 475-85. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 85
    - Equalization of Express Wages, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 86)
  - Sub-Series 475-86. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 86
    - 40-Hour Week, 1939-1945 (Box 608a, Folder 87)
  - Sub-Series 475-87. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 87
    - Increase in Wages, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 88)
  - Sub-Series 475-88. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 88
    - Election of Express Vice Grand President, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 89)
  - Sub-Series 475-89. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 89
    - Revision of Express Agreement, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 90)
  - Sub-Series 475-90. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 90
    - Elimination of Short-Hour Employment, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 91)
  - Sub-Series 475-91. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 91
    - Closed Shop, 1939-1949 (Box 608a, Folder 92)
  - Sub-Series 475-92. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 92
    - Legal Holidays, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 93)
  - Sub-Series 475-93. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 93
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Permit Optional Retirement After 25 Years' Service; Disability Retirement Regardless of Service, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 94)
  - Sub-Series 475-94. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 94
    - Amend Ritual, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 95)
  - Sub-Series 475-95. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 95
    - Amend By-Laws to Define Duties and Rights of Protective Committee, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 96)
  - Sub-Series 475-96. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 96
    - Grand Lodge Per Capita Tax on Hourly, Furloughed and Extra Employees, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 97)
  - Sub-Series 475-97. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 97
    - Amend By-Laws to Define Duties and Rights of Protective Committee, 1939 (Box 608a, Folder 98)
  - Sub-Series 475-98. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 98
    - Consolidations, Coordinations, Abandonments or Dissolutions of Existing Facilities, 1939-1946 (Box 608a, Folder 99)
  - Sub-Series 475-99. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 99
    - Free Transportation for Express Employees, 1939-1940 (Box 608a, Folder 100)
  - Sub-Series 475-100. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 100
    - Dispute Between American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations., 1939-1940 (Box 608a, Folder 101)
  - Sub-Series 475-101. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 101
    - Long Hours, 7-Day Assignments, Unemployment, 1946-1947 (Box 608a, Folder 102)
  - Sub-Series 475-101. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 101
    - Long Hours, 7-Day Assignments, Unemployment, 1939-1945 (Box 608a, Folder 103)
  - Sub-Series 475-103. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 103
    - Excepted or Personal Office Force Positions. 1939-1950 (Box 608a, Folder 104)
  - Sub-Series 475-104. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 104
    - Regulation of Competitive Transportation Facilities, 1939-1940 (Box 608a, Folder 105)
  - Sub-Series 475-105. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 105
    - Extend Washington Job Protection Agreement to Abandonments, 1939-1941 (Box 608a, Folder 106)
  - Sub-Series 475-106. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 106
    - Labor's Non-Partisan League, 1939-1940 (Box 608a, Folder 107)
  - Sub-Series 475-107. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 107
    - Federal Workmen's Compensation Act, 1939-1942 (Box 608a, Folder 108)
  - Sub-Series 475-108. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 108
    - No Discrimination Against Women Employees, 1939-1949 (Box 608b, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 475-109. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 109
    - Communism, Fascism, Nazism, 1939-1940 (Box 608b, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 475-110. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 110
    - Jurisdiction of International Brotherhood of Teamsters over Freight Handling, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 475-111. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 111
    - Differential in Wages Between Railroad and Express, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 475-112. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 112
    - Vacation and Sick Leave, Southern Pacific Railway, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 475-113. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 113
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Credit World War [I] Service, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 475-114. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 114
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Provide for Disability, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 475-115. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 115
    - Dee, R.P., 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 475-116. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 116
    - Prohibition of Quitting Time Between Midnight and 5:00 am, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 475-117. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 117
    - Compulsory Pooling of Less-than-Carload Freight, 1939-1941 (Box 608b, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 475-118. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 118
    - Shorter Work Day, 1939-1940 (Box 608b, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 475-119. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 119
    - Federal Health Insurance, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 475-120. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 120
    - Consolidations and Coordinations. 1939-1940 (Box 608b, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 475-121. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 121
    - Short-Hour Work, 1939-1941 (Box 608b, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 475-122. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 122
    - Vacations with Pay, 1939-1941 (Box 608b, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 475-123. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 123
    - Express General Foremen, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 475-124. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 124
    - Equalization of Express Wages, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 475-125. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 125
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Permit Optional Retirement After 25 Years' Service; Disability Retirement Regardless of Service, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 475-126. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 126
    - Elimination of Short-Hour Employment, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 475-127. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 127
    - 40-Hour Week, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 475-128. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 128
    - Wage Increase, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 475-129. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 129
    - Election of Express Vice Grand President, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 475-130. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 130
    - Revision of Express Agreement, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 475-131. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 131
    - Closed Shop, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 475-132. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 132
    - Legal Holidays, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 475-133. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 133
    - Vacations. 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 475-134. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 134
    - Wage Differential for Night Work, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 475-135. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 135
    - 6-Hour Day; 30-Hour Week, 1939-1940 (Box 608b, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 475-136. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 136
    - Dues for Pensioned Members, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 475-137. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 137
    - Mileage Base for Express Messengers, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 475-138. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 138
    - Federal Government Urged to Provide Educational Opportunities, 1939-1941 (Box 608b, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 475-139. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 139
    - Inland Waterways Corporation, 1939-1940 (Box 608b, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 475-140. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 140
    - Industry Committee, Fair Labor Standards Act, 1939-1940 (Box 608b, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 475-141. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 141
    - Labor. Grand Lodge Contribution to Subscriptions., 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 475-142. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 142
    - Promotion of Yard Clerks to Yardmaster, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 475-143. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 143
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Compel Retirement at Age 62, Permit Voluntary Retirement After 30 Years' Service and Disability Retirement After 5 Years' Service, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 475-144. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 144
    - Amend National Labor Relations Act, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 475-145. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 145
    - Refund Transportation Costs to Delegates, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 475-146. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 146
    - Vacation and Sick Leave, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 475-147. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 147
    - Colored Employees, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 475-148. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 148
    - Employees Entering Bunkers of Refrigerator Cars, 1939-1941 (Box 608b, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 475-149. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 149
    - State Legislative Committees, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 475-150. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 150
    - Job Protection, Consolidations, and Mergers, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 475-151. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 151
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Permit Retirement After 25 Years' Service; Disability Retirement Regardless of Service, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 475-152. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 152
    - Calculate Annuity on Years of Service Only, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 475-153. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 153